<resources>
  <string name="app_name">Toro v2</string>
  <string name="activity_show_case">Toro v2 Showcase</string>

  <string name="sample">
    GitHub Wiki is a simple way to let others contribute content. Any GitHub user can create and
    edit pages to use for documentation, examples, support, or anything you wish.
  </string>

  <string name="readme">
    Video list auto playback made simple, specially built for RecyclerView
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_4">
    Basic Sample 4: Official SimpleExoPlayerView
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_4_description">
    <![CDATA[This demo show the use of Official SimpleExoPlayerView.
    It is the same with Basic sample 1, accept for the Player View in used.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_1">
    Basic Sample 1: Minimal
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[In this sample, we learn how to implement very simple Video ViewHolder and Video list and
    add Toro support into the App.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_2">
    Basic Sample 2: Minimal, Ordered
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_2_description">
    <![CDATA[This basic example is similar to Basic Sample 1. Additionally, we have a feature to tell Toro
    which is the first Video we want to play.
    Until that Video is prepared and start playing, no other Videos is allowed to play.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_3">
    Basic Sample 3: Minimal, Loop, Interaction
  </string>

  <string name="basic_sample_3_description">
    <![CDATA[<p>This basic example is similar to Basic Sample 1 plus interaction with Video View.
    On single click, we temporarily pause the playback and show an AlertDialog, after we close that dialog, we resume the playback.
    We also provide custom feedback on long press too.</p>
    Furthermore, we add the ability to selective react to click event: we have different responses on the View user clicked.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="average_sample_1">
    Average Sample 1: Custom, Stateful
  </string>

  <string name="average_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[This example is similar to Basic Sample 1. But we add more complicated state listening event.
    So that we could see how ToroPlayer\'s callback works in practice.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="advance_sample_1">
    Advance Sample 1: Custom LayoutManager, Stateful playback
  </string>

  <string name="advance_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[This example is similar to Average Sample 1. This time, we use a custom LayoutManager
    (here I use CarouselLayoutManager) and implement ToroLayoutManager to get native support from Toro.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="facebook_sample_1">
    Custom Sample 1: Facebook + DialogFragment
  </string>

  <string name="facebook_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[This example introduce a Facebook-alike timeline, with mixed contents of Text and Videos.
    A click event to a Video will bring a \'Video list\' where requested Video is played as well as
    many suggested Videos.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="legacy_sample_1">
    Legacy Sample 1: Minimal, Legacy
  </string>

  <string name="legacy_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[<p>In this sample, we learn how to implement very simple Video ViewHolder and Video list and
    add Toro support into the App.</p>
    This sample use the legacy VideoView.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="extended_sample_1">
    Toro Extended Sample 1: Minimal, Powerful
  </string>

  <string name="extended_sample_1_description">
    <![CDATA[<p>In this sample, we learn how to use the extended benefit or Toro.</p>
    <p>The list will automatically scroll to next Player and trigger the playback.</p>
    A long click is handled to support more ideas in your Application.]]>
  </string>

  <string name="experiment">
    Experiment: about what is coming to Toro
  </string>

  <string name="experiment_description"><![CDATA[
    <p>This sample is the place I experiment the next features of Toro, but not be stable enough or even working.
    Some may be included in next version, some may not.</p>

    <p>It is not encourage to use it in production, but it is highly expected to have feedback as Github Issue.</p>

    This experiment includes:

    <ul>
      <li>Action button with various Add/Remove behaviours to verify how Toro works with Adapter#notify***</li>
      <li>Drag & drop to verify how Toro works with Adapter\'s data change in that case</li>
      <li>Click to open Single Player (portrait)</li>
    </ul>
    To be continued.
  ]]></string>

  <string name="title_activity_main">MainActivity</string>

  <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
  <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

  <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
  <string name="title_activity_demo">DemoActivity</string>
</resources>
